cd-wow.com 2019-06-13

# Help - Privacy Policy on WOW HD

### Deals

| 

## WOW HD Privacy Policy

## COMMITMENT TO YOUR PRIVACY

At WOW HD, your privacy is important to us. We understand that you entrust us with the management of your data. Please know that we protect your privacy. Under no circumstances will WOW HD sell or share any personal information about you to or with any person or organization except as provided in this Privacy Policy or as may be required by law or court order. This Privacy Policy describes the standards that we adhere to in handling information about you. 

The WOW HD website (the "Website") is provided to You by DirectToU, LLC and/or any of its related, affiliated and/or subsidiary companies (individually and collectively, "WOW HD," "We," "Our" or "Us"), and the following Privacy Policy applies to all of the services offered by WOW HD in connection with the Website as well as the WOW HD pages on Facebook, Twitter and MySpace. For convenience, the words "user," "You" and "Your" as used in this Privacy Policy refer to users of the Website. 

WOW HD recognizes that Your privacy and the protection of Your personal information are important to You, and therefore, has adopted this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy describes WOW HD's privacy practices and how WOW HD treats the personal information that it collects from You when You use the use the Website, including any personal information You provide when You conduct business with WOW HD on or through the Website or use WOW HD's Media's services that are provided on or through the Website. 

For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, "Personal Information" is information that (i) You provide to WOW HD and (ii) personally identifies You. Personal Information includes Your name, email and postal address, billing, credit card and banking information, telephone numbers and other data that can be used to personally identify or contact You. 

### THE INFORMATION WE OBTAIN AND MANAGE

The Personal Information that the WOW HD may collect from You and/or manage includes, but is not limited to: 

  * Contact information such as email and postal addresses and telephone numbers;
  * Credit card and banking information; and
  * Purchasing activities

Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, WOW HD will store all information provided by You in its secure data servers during the time You use WOW HD products and/or services. WOW HD uses commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that such information is secure and to protect against its loss, misuses, and alteration of the information under WOW HD's direct control. Notwithstanding the foregoing, WOW HD cannot guarantee that its security measures will prevent its computers from illegal or otherwise unauthorized access. For the avoidance of doubt, WOW HD will not retain Your credit card or other banking information without Your separate, prior written authorization. 

### HOW WE OBTAIN THE PERSONAL INFORMATION

WOW HD may obtain, collect, retain, store or otherwise maintain Your Personal Information from the following sources: 

  * Information that You provide to Us when You initiate communications with Us, subscribe to Our newsletter, respond to a survey published by Us or purchase goods and services from Us;
  * Your entries for sweepstakes and other promotions provided or sponsored by Us;
  * Your responses to communications from WOW HD. From time to time, WOW HD may communicate with You through email, postal mail or other forms of electronic communications regarding Your purchases of goods and services from Us and the Website. If You respond to these communications, Your responses may contain Personal Information; and
  * Third parties to whom You have provided Your Personal Information and have consented to those third parties sale, rental or transfer of such Personal Information.

You can decline to provide Your Personal Information to WOW HD by not engaging in the activities described above. If You decline to submit Personal Information, WOW HD may not be able to or may choose not to provide to You some or all of the features available on the Website. 

WOW HD also collects non-personally identifiable server-log information relating to users of the Website. This information, may include information such as, but not limited to Your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of Your request, date and time of access, one or more cookies that may uniquely identify Your browser and referrer Uniform Resource Locator. None of this information enables WOW HD to personally identify or contact You. 

### HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

WOW HD only uses Personal Information for the purposes and in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. Specifically, WOW HD only uses Your Personal Information for: 

  * Doing business with You, including processing payments and communicating with You regarding Your purchases of goods and services from WOW HD;
  * Communicating with You regarding sweepstakes and other contests offered or sponsored by WOW HD that You have entered;
  * Processing, formatting and displaying customized content on the Website for You;
  * Communicating with You regarding changes to: WOW HD's Terms of Service, this Privacy Policy or any other policies or terms relating to the Website or the offering of goods and services on the Website;
  * Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve the Website and the other goods and services offered or provided by WOW HD;
  * Communicating with You, with Your consent, regarding new and additional WOW HD services and changes to the Website; and/or
  * Ensuring the technical functioning of the Website, including creating and maintaining back-ups or other archival copies of Personal Information and other related data.

WOW HD restricts access to Personal Information to those employees, contractors and agents of WOW HD who need to access Personal Information for the purposes specified above. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination, if they fail to meet these obligations. 

Except as otherwise set forth herein, WOW HD does not share Your Personal Information with third parties without Your consent, except when We believe that it is reasonably necessary to do so in order to comply with a subpoena or other judicial order or process, as otherwise required by law or in order to enforce WOW HD's Terms of Service. In such circumstances, Your Personal Information may also be disclosed to WOW HD's attorneys. 

If WOW HD desires to use Your Personal Information for any purpose other than those described in this Privacy Policy, WOW HD will request Your consent prior to such use and offer You an effective way to opt out of the use of Personal Information for those other purposes. If You opt out or otherwise decline to submit Personal Information in response to such a request, WOW HD may not be able to provide to You some or all of the features available on the Website. 

### TECHNICAL INFORMATION

We may collect and track certain technical information to ensure that Your experiences on the Website and purchase of goods and services offered on the Website, including but not limited to the following: 

  * Cookies - a cookie is a small file stored on a user's computer that contains information about the user. We may use either session ID cookies (which terminate once a browser is closed) or persistent cookies (which are small text files stored on a user's hard drive for an extended period of time). Cookies allow Us to see how and when You use our sites, but they cannot be used to track personal information such as email address or phone number. Cookies also allow Us to store the personal preferences that You set during each visit to our sites which can speed up Your future visits. These cookies cannot damage a user's files and cannot read information from a user's hard drive.
  * Log files - WOW HD may use log files to track how our sites are being accesses and used. Log files track anonymous user information such as IP addresses, browser types, Internet service providers, referring and exit pages, platform type, date and time stamps, and number of clicks to, from, and within our sites.
  * Information from Banner Ads - if You arrive at WOW HD's website(s) through a banner ad or other Affiliate referral device, WOW HD may track where You arrived from, as well as clicks that might have impacted our servers.
  * We may use clear GIF Tracking Pixels to track user movement through our web sites for aggregated site traffic measuring. In addition, some Affiliates may set such tracking pixels on our web site pages to track completed forms and requests referred by their web sites.

Please be assured that no Personal Information is collected from or stored in these cookies, files or tracking devices. 

### "CONTACT US" INFORMATION

If You communicate with Us through the "Contact Us," We may ask You for Personal Information such as Your name, email address, or phone number. If You are contacting Us with respect to a customer service issue, we may use the Personal Information that You provide to contact You in order to resolve that customer service issue. If necessary to resolve Your customer service issue, the Personal Information that You provide to Us may be shared with third parties in order to resolve the issue. Please understand that by providing such information in connection with a customer service issue, You are giving Your express consent for Us to use Your Personal Information to contact and communicate with You regarding that customer service issue. 

### THIRD PARTY INFORMATION

WOW HD may collect or purchase information from third parties regarding persons who provided information to those third parties. Information provided to Us by the third party may include, but not limited to, individual names, email and postal addresses, telephone numbers, and any other information provided to the third party. WOW HD uses its reasonable best efforts to ensure that (i) the third party possesses the right to transfer the information to WOW HD and (ii) WOW HD has received the right to communicate with the persons who provided the information. 

### EMAIL SOLICITATIONS

WOW HD only sends email solicitation to users who have agreed, through this Privacy Policy, on third party websites or by other means, to receive emails from WOW HD. 

### WIRELESS COMMUNICATIONS

If the email address You provide to WOW HD is a wireless address, You agree to receive messages at such address from WOW HD. You understand that Your wireless carrier's standard rates apply to these messages. You represent and warrant that You are the owner or authorized user of the wireless device on which messages will be received, and that You are authorized to approve the applicable charges associated therewith. 

### AFFILIATES 

WOW HD may share Your Personal Information with companies that are related to or affiliated with WOW HD (collectively, “Affiliates”). Affiliates will use Your Personal Information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

### LINKS

This Privacy Policy only pertains to the Website. Other websites and portals, such as those to which the Website links to or link to the Website, including, without limitation, Facebook.com, MySpace.com and Twitter.com may have their own privacy policies. We encourage You to read the privacy policies and terms of use of the websites and portals that You visit through links placed on the Website as well as those for websites that provide links to the Website. You should contact these websites directly if You have any questions about their use of Your Personal Information. WOW HD is not responsible for any use of Your Personal Information or any other type of Your information when You use such third party sites and services. 

### INFORMATION SHARING AND ONWARD TRANSFER

WOW HD reserves the right to sell, rent or otherwise share some or all of Your Personal Information with other companies or individuals outside of WOW HD if: 

  * You have consented to such sale, rental or sharing; and/or
  * WOW HD becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of all of its assets. In such circumstances, WOW HD will provide notice before Personal Information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

In addition, WOW HD reserves the right to share non-personally identifiable information relating to users of the Website or the WOW HD services with our partners and advertisers. The information will not be linked to any personal identifiable information. When You sign up for any third party service, information may be shared with the third party and Your privacy will be maintained in accordance with the third party privacy policy. 

### RESTRICTED AREAS

Certain areas of the Website such as areas only available to our Affiliate and/or customer network, may have additional or different terms and conditions than those addressed in this policy. If You access any of these areas, You should consult the privacy policies posted in those areas. 

### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

WOW HD may, at its sole discretion, revise this Privacy Policy at any time in a manner consistent with applicable laws and regulations. When we revise this policy, including changes to WOW HD's use of Your Personal Information, we will incorporate the revisions into this policy and will revise the "last revised" date at the top of this web page. We will notify you when any changes to this Privacy Policy are made. We recommend that You review those changes in order to remain informed about how WOW HD uses Your Personal Information. 

### CALIFORNIA USER CONSUMER RIGHTS

In accordance with California Civil Code Sec. 1789.3, California resident users are entitled to know that they may file grievances and complaints with the California Department of Consumer Affairs, 400 R Street, STE 1080, Sacramento, CA 95814; or by telephone at (916) 445-1254 or (800) 952-5210; or by email to [dca@dca.ca.gov](mailto:dca@dca.ca.gov). For more information about protecting Your privacy, You may wish to visit: [www.ftc.gov](http://www.ftc.gov/). 

### CHILDREN'S/MINOR'S USE OF THE WEBSITE

Consistent with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent. 

### USE OF THE WEBSITE

You acknowledge that the personal information You provide to WOW HD is collected and stored in the United States and therefore consent to the transfer of information to and storage of the information in the United States, regardless of Your country of domicile. 

### SEVERABILITY

If any provision of this Privacy Policy is found to be illegal, void, or unenforceable, that provision will be deemed severed from the balance of the agreement and will not affect the validity and enforceability of the remaining provisions, which will continue in full force and effect. 

### ACKNOWLEDGEMENT

By completing forms provided by WOW HD and providing personal information through the Website, through any means, and by using the Website and services contained therein, You hereby represent and warrant that: 

  * You have read, understand and agree to WOW HD's Privacy Policy;
  * You are an actual person of at least 18 years of age, You have the right to provide the information that You submit to WOW HD, and the information You submit is accurate, complete and truthful; and 
  * If You do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, then do not provide Your information to WOW HD through any means. In such case, WOW HD is relieved of any of its obligations to You as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

If You have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [support@wowhd.com](mailto:support@wowhd.com).   
  
---|---
